{
    "id": "0750881c041d4692b5c3e0a3d632a6a8",
    "title": "Irregular Verbs",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ea01e57ca38a4d1086b04fdf460e6763",
            "title": "Irregular Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I .................................... the bell twice.",
                    "description": "Rang is the simple past of ring.",
                    "answers": [
                        "rang",
                        "ringed",
                        "rung"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you ....................................... the violin?",
                    "description": "Brought is the simple past of bring.",
                    "answers": [
                        "bringed",
                        "brought"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The cat has ....................................... the milk.",
                    "description": "Drunk is the past participle form of drink.",
                    "answers": [
                        "drank",
                        "drinked",
                        "drunk"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ..................................... the work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "done",
                        "do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They ...................................... a well in the backyard.",
                    "description": "Dug is the past simple and past participle of dig. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "dig",
                        "digged",
                        "dug"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ...................................... the clothes out.",
                    "description": "The past simple of wring is wrang or wrung. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "wringed",
                        "wrang",
                        "wrung"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has ..................................... a lot on his children's education.",
                    "description": "Spent is the past simple and past participle form of spend.",
                    "answers": [
                        "spent",
                        "spend",
                        "spended"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How you have ....................................!",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "grew",
                        "growed",
                        "grown"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have ........................................ to Australia.",
                    "description": "We use been for finished visit. If somebody has gone to Australia, they are still in Australia. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "gone",
                        "been",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The place ........................................ like a sewer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stink",
                        "stinked",
                        "stank"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Peter ......................................... under his breath.",
                    "description": "Sweared is possible in a careless style. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "sweared",
                        "swore",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They ......................................... the grains into powder.",
                    "description": "Ground is the past simple of grind. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "grinded",
                        "grounded",
                        "ground"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}